let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Which one of the following is an example of a valid C# variable name?",
    answer: "myVar",
    options: ["myVar", "3myVar", "My-Var", "_myVar"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid C# data type? ",
    answer: "StringBuilder",
    options: ["int", "double", "string", "StringBuilder"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the correct syntax to declare a variable in C#?",
    answer: "var x;",
    options: ["var x;", "x = new var;", "int x;", "x var;"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a valid C# data type?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: ["Integer", "String", "Boolean", "All of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "What is the correct data type to represent a single character in C#?",
    answer: "char",
    options: ["int", "float", "char", "string"],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a single line comment in C#?",
    answer: "// comment",
    options: ["// comment", "/* comment */", "# comment", "-- comment"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What data type would you use to store a whole number?",
    answer: "int",
    options: ["int", "string", "float", "double"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is not a C# data type?",
    answer: "object",
    options: ["int", "string", "double", "object"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a multi-line comment in C#?",
    answer: "/* This is a multi-line comment */",
    options: [
      "// This is a multi-line comment",
      "/* This is a multi-line comment */",
      "# This is a multi-line comment",
      "** This is a multi-line comment **",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "What is the output of the following C# code? Console.WriteLine(&#x22;Hello, World!&#x22;);",
    answer: "Hello, World!",
    options: [
      "HELLO, WORLD!",
      "Hello, World!",
      "hello, world!",
      "None of the above",
    ],
  },
];
